Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS.180
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence, 194848
  - Series I, Subseries A: Individuals and Institutions, 195163
    - LuhringAugustine / Lauren Wittels, 1992; 195607 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Lukas & Sternberg Inc. / Caroline Schneider, Undated; 195606 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Lupo, Bob, 2000; 195605 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Lupton, Catherine, 1975-1998; 195604 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Lusitania Press, Inc., 1993; 195603 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Lutwak, Mark & Y York, 1992; 195602 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Lyssiotis, Peter, Undated; 195601 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Mabou Mines, 2001; 195600 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - MacAliser, Helen, 1996-1997; 195599 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - McAlpin, Loring, 1990; 195598 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - McCaffery, Larry, 1994-1995; 195597 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - McCloy, Crosby, 1995-1996; 195596 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - McCook, Patrick, Undated; 195595 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - McCurdy, Betty and Joseph, 1990-2002; 195594 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1991-2004; 195593 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - McEwen, Christian, 2000-2002; 195592 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - McFries, Gillian, [2000]-2002; 195591 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - McGrath, Patrick, 1984-2002; 195590 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - McLean, Jack, 1991; 195589 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - McMahon, Jeff, 1999; 195588 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - McPhen, Bill / The Stanford University Libraries, 1986; 195587 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - MAD ALEX Arts Foundation, Inc., 1995; 195586 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Magill, Mark, 1983-1984; 195585 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Makishi, Stacy, 1994-2000; 195584 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Maliszewski, Paul / Denver Quarterly, 2003; 195583 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Malloy, Judy, c.a. 1982; 195582 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - MAMM Magazine, Undated; 195581 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Manchester, Robert, 1998; 195580 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Mander, Bill, 1985; 195579 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Manheim, Kate, Undated; 195578 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Manske, Eva, 1994; 195577 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Manson, David, Undated; 195576 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Mantegna, GianFranco, 1982; 195575 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Maren, Michael and Dani Shapiro, 1999; 195574 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Margolin, Deb, 1997; 195573 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Marian Goodman Gallery, 2001; 195572 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Marlowe & Company, 1995; 195571 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Marsden, Simon, 1984; 195570 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Marshall, Bertie, 1996; 195569 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Marshall, Robert, Undated; 195568 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Martin, Douglas A., c.a. 2000; 195567 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Martin, Katy, [2001]; 195566 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Martin, Sarah, 1995; 195565 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Martin Secker & Warburg, 1997; 195564 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Mathews, Harry, 1976-2001; 195563 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Mathews, Marie, 2003; 195562 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - The Media Show, 1988; 195561 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Mella, Leanne and Mark Segal, 2000; 195560 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Mellor, Simon, 1991; 195559 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Meltzer, Richard, 1978-1996; 195558 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - The Menil Collection, 1999-2000; 195557 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Mernin, Brendan, 1995-1997; 195556 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Meyer, Lisa, 1999; 195555 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Michael Meller Literary Agency, 1997; 195554 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Michell, J., 1975; 195553 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Middlebury College, 1991; 195552 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Miller, Doris, 1996; 195551 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Milne, Drew, 2000; 195550 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Minnigh, Joost, Undated; 195549 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Ministerie Van Cultuur, Recreatie En Maatschappelijk Werk (Ministry of Culture, Recreation and Social Work), 1975; 195548 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Miyake, Ayumi, 2003; 195547 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Mobley, Jane (Philip and Sarah), c.a. 1993; 195546 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Moe, David, Shari and Cameron, 1997; 195545 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - [Mom and Dad], c.a. 1983; 195544 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Monte, Dan, 1992; 195543 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Moody, 1995; 195542 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Moonstone Inc.: Education Through The Arts, 1991; 195541 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Morawetz, Silvia, 1989-2000; 195540 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Morin-Watson, C., 1997; 195539 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Morrison, Irma, 1993; 195538 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Morrison, Martha, 1994; 195537 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Morrison, Toni, 1993; 195536 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Morrow, Rodger, 1995-2005; 195535 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Mosaic Press, 1991-2005; 195534 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Moschovakis, Anna (Restricted), 1992-2001; 195533 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Moss, Lynne and Donald, 1993-1999; 195532 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Mouly, Francoise / RAW BOOKS, 1980-1981; 195531 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Mt. Hood Community College, 1991; 195530 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Mruczynschi, Josef, Undated; 195529 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Mueller, Dan, 1994; 195528 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Mullen, Ruth and Jim Bradley, 1992; 195527 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Murakami, Takashi, 2001; 195526 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Murray, Tatyana, 2002; 195525 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Museum Boymans-van Beuningen Rotterdam, 1992; 195524 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - The Museum of Contemporary Art (Los Angeles), 1999; 195523 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - The Museum of Contemporary Photography, 1997; 195522 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 2000; 195521 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The Museum of Modern Art (New York), 1981-2004; 195520 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Museum of Modern Art at Heide, Australia, 1996; 195519 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Nachtigall, Richard, M.D., 1993; 195518 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Nadotti, Maria, 1993; 195517 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Naropa University Summer Writing Program, 1999; 195516 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - The National Book Critics Circle, 1999; 195515 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1990; 195514 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Natt, Rochelle, Undated; 195513 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Nearly Fatal Women / The Knitting Factory, Undated; 195512 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Neary, Scott D., 1978-1993; 195511 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Nebel, John, 1992-1993; 195510 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, Undated; 195509 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Neilson, Melanie, 1991-1993; 195508 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Nemet-Nejat, Murat, 1993; 195507 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Neri, Louise, 1999; 195506 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - nest: A Quarterly Magazine of Interiors, 1998-2002; 195505 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Neurath, Thomas, 1981; 195504 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - New Directions: Publishing Corporation, 2001; 195503 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - New Langdon Arts, 1988; 195502 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - New Literary History, 1987-1988; 195501 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - The New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1985-1998; 195500 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - New Observations, 1984-1997; 195499 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1991-1999; 195498 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - New York Institute for the Humanities at NYU, 2004; 195497 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - The New York Public Library, Undated; 195496 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - The New York State Council on the Arts / Gregory Kolovakos / Jewelle L. Gomez, 1988-1993; 195495 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - The New York Times, 1989-2000; 195494 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - New York University, 1999-2004; 195493 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - NYU Medical Center, 2000-2002; 195492 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - NYU Press, 2002; 195491 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - The New Yorker, 1983-2001; 195490 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Newman, John, Undated; 195489 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Newsday, 1997; 195488 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Newton, David, 1996-2002; 195487 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Nicholson, Annable, 1974; 195486 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Nicolazzini, Piergiorgio, 1998; 195485 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Niedzviecki, Hal, 1995-1999; 195484 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - NIGHT, 1991-1995; 195483 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Niimoto, Riyo, Undated; 195482 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Noble, Aaron, c.a. 1984; 195481 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Norton, Margot, 1988; 195480 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Novakov, Anna, 1991; 195479 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Nufer, Doug, 1998; 195478 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Nutting, Cherie, 1995-2002; 195477 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - O'Toole, Laurence, 1997; 195476 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Obst, Deiter, 1984-1989; 195475 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Odell, David, 1976; 195474 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - The Ohio State University, 1995; 195473 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Oisteanu, Valery and Ruth, 1985; 195472 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Oklahoma State University, Undated; 195471 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - One Meadway, 1990; 195470 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Oppenheim, Lisa, 2001; 195469 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Oppenheim, Meret, 1973-1980; 195468 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Oregon Art Institute, Northwest Film & Video Center, 1991; 195467 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Orr, Carol Wallace, 1991; 195466 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Otcu, Onder, 2002; 195465 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Otis School of Art and Design, 1993; 195464 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Owens, Jim and Bette, 1993-2000; 195463 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Özkaya, Serkan, 1997-1998; 195462 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Pace University, 1993; 195461 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Pantheon Books, 1985; 195460 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - PARKETT: Art Magazine / Kunstzeitschrift, 1992-1995; 195459 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Passagen Verlag, 1994-1995; 195458 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Pavillion Books, 1994-1999; 195457 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Pauter, Nicole, 1997; 195456 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Pearl, Monica, 1995; 195455 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - PEN American Center, 1998-2005; 195454 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Penguin, 1990-2002; 195453 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Penny, Bridget, 1993-1999; 195452 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Pera, Brian, Undated; 195451 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Perlman, Cara, 1996; 195450 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Petropoulos, Renee, 2000; 195449 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Phaidon Press Limited, 1994-1997; 195448 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Phillips, Caryl (Caz), 1991-1999; 195447 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Phillips, Christopher, 1976; 195446 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Piper, Adrian, Undated; 195445 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Plantenga, Bart, c.a. 1991; 195444 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Plate, Peter, 1992-1993; 195443 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Ploof, John, 1997; 195442 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Ploughshares / Paul Muldoon, 1999-2000; 195441 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - The Poetry Project, 1996-1999; 195440 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Points de Fuite, 1994; 195439 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Pollock, Jim, 1994; 195438 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 2002; 195437 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Poorbaugh, Cindy, 1995-1997; 195436 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Porter, Joe Ashby, 2005; 195435 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Poseidon Press, 1987-1993; 195434 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Preiss, Jeff, 1995-1996; 195433 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Preserved Fish Productions, 1998; 195432 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Prina, Stephen, 1986-1995; 195431 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Prince, Richard, 1984; 195430 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Prior, Amy, 1997-2002; 195429 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Proctor, Minna, 2001; 195428 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Public Art Fund, 1991; 195427 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Pullinger, Kate, 1990-1999; 195426 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Purdy, James, Undated; 195425 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Purdy, Janet, Undated; 195424 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Pushcart Press, 1985-2004; 195423 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Quackenbush, Jan, 1988; 195422 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Rabinowitz, Jon, 1997-2001; 195421 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Raff, Orit, 2000; 195420 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Raftery, Karen, 1993; 195419 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Rain Taxi: Review of Books, 1996; 195418 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Rainer, Yvonne, 1991-2000; 195417 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Rampike, Undated; 195416 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1996; 195415 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Random House, 1985-2004; 195414 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Rankin, Aimee, 1987; 195413 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Rattray, David, 1977-1985; 195412 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Reaktion Books Ltd, 1998; 195411 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Recorded Books, 2005; 195410 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Red Bass, 1988; 195409 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Redstone Press, 1992; 195408 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Reed, Judith, 1993; 195407 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Regan, Marie, 2004; 195406 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Reiner, 1996; 195405 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - La République Internationale des Lettres / Noël Blandin, 1993; 195404 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Rertzelos, Pauline, Undated; 195403 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Rettallade, Joan, 1999; 195402 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Review of Contemporary Fiction, Undated; 195401 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Rexroth, Stevie, 1995; 195400 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Rhett, Kathryn, 1996; 195399 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Ribot, Marc, 1993-1996; 195398 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Rice, Doug, Undated; 195397 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Ridgefield Press, 1992; 195396 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Riley, (Elizabeth) Denise, 1991-2002; 195395 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Robbins, Jack, 1976; 195394 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - The Robert Lantz - Joy Harris Literary Agency, Inc., 1990-1996; 195393 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Rochon, Sidonie, 1975-2001; 195392 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Rochou, Aidocie, 2003; 195391 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Roeseler, Karl, 1997-2001; 195390 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Rohn, Bob, 1985; 195389 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Root, Jane / The Media Show, 1988; 195388 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Rose, Joel and Catherine Texier / Love on the Edge, 1991-1992; 195387 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Rosenberg, Alan, 2002; 195386 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Rosenberg, Aura, 1995-1998; 195385 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Ross, Andrew, 1997-2001; 195384 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Ross, Melanie, 1997; 195383 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Ross-Erikson, Inc., Publishers, 1976; 195382 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Rothenberger, Manfred, 1990; 195381 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Rowe, Marsha, 1991-1993; 195380 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Rower, Ann, Undated; 195379 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - The Russian Samovar / James [Wilson], 2003; 195378 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - S. Fischer Verlag, 1997; 195377 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Sabin, Stefana, 1992-1998; 195376 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Saint Mark's Bookshop, 1983; 195375 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - St. Martin's Press, 1995; 195374 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Salerno, Linda, 2000; 195373 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Art Institute, 1990; 195372 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sanford J. Greenburger Associates Inc., 1996; 195371 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Sarah Lazin Books, 1999; 195370 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Saul, Paul, 2007; 195369 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Scalapino, Leslie, 1995; 195368 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Scalo (re: Roni Horn), 1997; 195367 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Schambelan, Elizabeth, Undated; 195366 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Schlupmann, Heide, Undated; 195365 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Schmeiser, Jo, 1996; 195364 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Schoffelen, Jos, 1971-2003; 195363 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Scholder, Amy ***see also*** High Risk ***see also*** Serpent's Tail, 1988-1998; 195362 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - School of Visual Arts, Photography Department, 2003; 195361 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Schouten, Lydia, 1992-1998; 195360 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Scott, James and Yolanda Orozco, 1991-1999; 195359 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Scott, Susan, 1999; 195358 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Screen Actors Guild - Producers Pension And Health Plans, 1999; 195357 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Scribner / Simon & Schuster, Inc., 2001; 195356 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Scrivner, Jay ***see also*** Stadler, Matthew, 1993; 195355 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Searle, Adrian, 1996; 195354 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - the Seattle Review, 2004; 195353 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Second Shift, 1992-1993; 195352 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Segrave, Elisa, 1991-1993; 195351 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Seigle, Iris, 1995; 195350 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Seigle, Jane, 1987-1997; 195349 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Seigle, Robert, 1987-1997; 195348 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Seip, Mattijn, c.a. 2000; 195347 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Seltzer, Hara, 1995-1999; 195346 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Semiotext(e), 2001; 195345 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Sengupta, Somini and Hans van de Weerd, 2000-2004; 195344 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Seriously Inc./Management for Living Colour, 1992; 195343 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Serpent's Tail, 1988-2003; 195342 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Seven Stories, 1999; 195341 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Shakespeare & Co. Bookstore, 1990; 195340 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Shapiro-Maren, Dani, Michael and Jacob, 2000; 195339 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Sharpe, Matt, 2002; 195338 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Shaver, Nancy, 1997; 195337 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Shaviro, Steve, 1994; 195336 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Sheck, Laurie, Undated; 195335 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Sheffield, Elizabeth and Jeffrey, 1998; 195334 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Sherman, Cindy, 2001-2002; 195333 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Shimo, Seiichiro, 1988; 195332 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Shohl, David, 1996-1999; 195331 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Shore, Stephen/Staphan and Ginger, c.a. 2005; 195330 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Sickels, Amy, 2004; 195329 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Sikorski, Rob, Undated; 195328 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Sillman, Amy, 1977-2002; 195327 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Silverberg, Ira ***see also*** High Risk *** see also*** Serpent's Tail, 1992-2004; 195326 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Simmons, Laurie, 1992; 195325 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Simon & Schuster, Undated; 195324 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Small Press Traffic, 2001; 195323 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Donny, 1996-1997; 195322 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Smith, Kiki, 1984-1999; 195321 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Seton, c.a. 2000; 195320 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1981; 195319 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Snedman, Lorna, 1984; 195318 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - S.I.T.T. (Societe Internationale Transit Transport), c.a. 1985; 195317 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Society For The Right To Die, c.a. 1991; 195316 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Soft Skull Press, 2005; 195315 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Sohn, Miyoung, 1998; 195314 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1996; 195313 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Sonberg, Warren, 1970-1993; 195312 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Song, Suran, 1996-2001; 195311 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Sorrentino, Christopher, 2005; 195310 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - The South Bank Centre, 1990; 195309 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - South Street Seaport Museum, 2002; 195308 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Spahr, Juliana, Undated; 195307 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Sphinx, 1987; 195306 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Springfield, Susan, 1981-1998; 195305 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Spuyten Duyvil, 2000; 195304 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Stadler, Matthew, 1992-2002; 195303 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Stallings, Tyler, 1991-1995; 195302 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Stanford University Libraries, 1986; 195301 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - SUNY Buffalo, 1991; 195300 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1995-2005; 195299 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Steiner, Eurydice, 1996-2001; 195298 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Steinke, Darcey, 1998-1999; 195297 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Sterling-Pierce Co., Inc., 1997; 195296 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Stern, Lesley, 1982-1997; 195295 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Stockholder, Jessica, 1995-2000; 195294 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Stone, Andrew, Undated; 195293 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Stone, Susan, 1985; 195292 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Stop Over Press, 1994-1996; 195291 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Stop the War, 1983; 195290 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Storrie, Calum, [1994]; 195289 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Stroemfeld/Roter Stern, 1985-1998; 195288 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - SUN, 1981; 195287 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Sung, Stella C. Y., 1997; 195286 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Surface Tension: Lesbian, Straight and Bisexual Women Write About Their Friendships / Meg Daly, 1994; 195285 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Sweitzer, Jody / TAB, 1996; 195284 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Swift, Graham, 1993-2000; 195283 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Synchronization, 2003; 195282 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Tabbi, Joseph, 1997; 195281 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Tamang, Indra, 2000; 195280 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Tantimedh, Adisakdi, 1990-1991; 195279 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Tax, Sissi, c.a. 2002; 195278 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Tessa, David, 1973; 195277 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Tewes, Robin, 1997-1999; 195276 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Third Wave Foundation, 1997; 195275 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Thorne, Ann, 1999; 195274 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Tickner, Lisa, 1985; 195273 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Time Out, 1996-2000; 195272 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Tin House Magazine, 1999-2000; 195271 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Tinling, David C., 1991; 195270 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Tinney, Christopher, c.a. 2000; 195269 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Tobier, Nick, 1999-2000; 195268 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Toibin, Colm, 1992-1997; 195267 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Topolski, Teresa, 1992; 195266 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Topp, Mike, 199-; 195265 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Torberg, Peter, 1995-1998; 195264 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Toshiba, 1998; 195263 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Treadwell, Elizabeth, 1999-2000; 195262 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Trinidad, David, 1983-2003; 195261 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Trip Street Press, 1995-2001; 195260 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Trippi, Laura, 1996; 195259 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Tronnier, Claudia, 1988; 195258 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Trophy Nut Co., 1996; 195257 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Truitt, Sam, 2005; 195256 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Tsyskus, Gork, 1977; 195255 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Turtle Point Press / Jonathan D. Rabinowitz, 2001; 195254 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Turyn, Anne, 1995-1997; 195253 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Tuttle-Mori Agency, 1991-1999; 195252 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Tyer, Brad, 1991; 195251 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Tyler Galleries, Tyler School of Art, Temple University, 1995; 195250 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Ulin, David L., 1993; 195249 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Ultimatum, Undated; 195248 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - UPS, 1997; 195247 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - United University Professions, Undated; 195246 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - University Art Museum, SUNY Albany, 2003; 195245 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - University of Maryland, Baltimore County, Center for Art and Visual Culture, 2005; 195244 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - University of Pennsylvania, The School of Veterinary Medicine, 2001; 195243 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - The University of Tennessee Press, 1991; 195242 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Unmuzzled Ox: Books & Magazine, 1988; 195241 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Urchueguia, Cristina and KD Wolff, 2002; 195240 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Valentine, Jean, 2002; 195239 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Van den Bosch, Annette, 1984-1985; 195238 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Vaughn, Allan, c.a. 1965; 195237 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Venero, Isabel, 2006; 195236 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Venezky, Elie, c.a. 1994; 195235 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - The Venus Girls, 1987; 195234 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - verlagsauslieferungen, 1984-1985; 195233 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Vermont College of Norwich University, MFA in Visual Art, 1999; 195232 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Veronese, David, Undated; 195231 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Viegener, Matias, 1990-1995; 195230 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Viking / Penguin Books Ltd, 1988; 195229 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - The Village Voice, 1991-1999; 195228 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Vintage / Random House UK Ltd., 1998-1999; 195227 (Box 6, Folder 151)